In home now
现在在家
I'm not going
我不去
Everyone has
每个人都有
Lol opening
哈哈开口
I have no idea
我没有注意了
Goggles goggles
护目镜
Safety first
安全第一
You do not need this
你不需要这个
No
没有
Well I think so well
好吧，我觉得很好
Core
核心
Kinda like a Cyprus in the kid that said in the back of the class is actually pretty fun
Kinda像塞浦路斯的孩子一样，在班级后面说实际上很有趣
Probably did a little too
大概也做了一点
It was not as crumble
没那么崩溃
Contact when they are there
他们在那里时联系
I hit him too hard that one night
那天晚上我对他打得太重了
If you like these are one
如果你喜欢这些是一个
Beautiful honest
美丽诚实
This one at 4
This is a
这是一个
Pictures of bad boy in there you have to put it in the summer and put it in a long
那里坏男孩的照片，您必须在夏天放好，然后放很长
Wine
葡萄酒
Oh yeah
哦耶
We're going to hold it so that it doesn't
我们将要持有它，以便它不会
Go into your eyes
进入你的眼睛
Not done Force too hard
未完成太用力了
Otherwise you'll break the entire
否则你会破坏整个
Not in the middle of it will seem right down the middle hair
不在中间的地方似乎就在中间的头发上
I would think
我会认为
You get the screwdriver in the same and give it a whack
您将螺丝刀放在同一把螺丝刀中
Do you want me to do with the way my mother used to do it
你想让我跟我妈妈过去一样吗
Inside this
里面这个
To try putting it up so your history on Steam
尝试把它放在您的Steam上的历史上
A crack a walnut here
核桃在这里
This is not a difficult task but you do need to make sure that you get the right in to start with
这不是一项艰巨的任务，但是您需要确保自己正确地开始
No problem it will open that way but that's a little bit messy around your kitchen
没问题，它会以这种方式打开，但是厨房周围有点混乱
So my favourite method inside and outside they're all this
所以我最喜欢的内部和外部方法都是
This is where you don't want to be
这是你不想成为的地方
Put the sky over
So that you can see your flat inside on the bottom of a walnut
这样一来，您就可以在胡桃木的底部看到自己的内胆
And there usually is a little bit of a crack right in there and this is your point of entry into your wallet if
而且通常那里会有一点裂缝，这是您进入钱包的起点，如果
When somebody is banging with a hammer
当有人用锤子敲打
You can use anything
你可以用任何东西
Cut your hair
剪头发
Going gently
轻轻地走
Twist
捻
It should be cleanly and
它应该干净并且
I've never done this before but just on the edge of a spatula
我以前从未做过，只是在锅铲的边缘
Safe to use
使用安全
They should be all that we need
他们应该是我们所需要的
I'm going to find that openings
我会找到那个空缺
Going to stick the corner of the spatula in there
会把刮刀的角落粘在那里
If you don't
如果你不这样做
Who was the actual top of the Nutcracker
谁是胡桃夹子的真正顶峰
And this guy is actually designed to do this
这个家伙实际上是专为此目的而设计的
Simple enough to just putting a knife in between the Nutcracker
非常简单，只需在胡桃夹子之间放一把刀
And tracking it
并跟踪它
It comes apart amazing how well
令人惊讶的是效果如何